<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- ~ SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2026 INFO.nl -->
<!-- ~ SPDX-License-Identifier: EUPL-1.2+ -->
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.4.xsd">
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-54513 affects jackson-databind's BasicPolymorphicTypeValidator.Builder.allowIfSubTypeIsArray().
            This vulnerable jackson-databind version is only pulled in transitively (via
            org.wildfly.security:wildfly-elytron-jose-util -> wildfly-elytron-http-oidc) into the providedCompile
            and providedRuntime configurations, which are compile-only scope against APIs supplied by WildFly at
            deploy time and are not packaged into the deployable artifact.
            Neither this codebase nor the WildFly Elytron libraries that pull in this version call
            allowIfSubTypeIsArray() or use polymorphic type validation at all (verified by searching the compiled
            classes of wildfly-elytron-jose-util, wildfly-elytron-jose-jwk, wildfly-elytron-http-oidc and
            wildfly-elytron-auth), so the vulnerable code path is unreachable.
            The actual application runtime and compile classpaths already resolve jackson-databind to the fixed
            2.22.1 version via the jackson-bom pin in gradle/libs.versions.toml.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/com\.fasterxml\.jackson\.core/jackson-databind@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54513</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-41851 is a DoS caused by unbounded cache growth in Spring Expression Language (SpEL)
            evaluation, specifically in the org.springframework.expression.spel package shipped in the
            spring-expression artifact.
            spring-core and spring-beans are only pulled in transitively via org.flowable:flowable-engine, which
            uses them for utility classes (e.g. BeanUtils, ClassUtils), not for SpEL evaluation. Flowable evaluates
            its own `${...}` expressions in BPMN/CMMN definitions using its own JUEL-based expression engine, not
            Spring's SpelExpressionParser.
            The spring-expression artifact that contains the vulnerable class is not a dependency of this project
            at all (confirmed absent from both the compileClasspath and runtimeClasspath configurations), so the
            vulnerable code path is unreachable regardless of the spring-core/spring-beans version present.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.springframework/spring-(core|beans)@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41851</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-41850 (SpEL algorithmic complexity DoS), CVE-2026-41848 (AntPathMatcher ReDoS),
            CVE-2026-41842 (Spring MVC/WebFlux static resource DoS) and CVE-2026-41838 (predictable
            spring-websocket session IDs) all require a Spring module that is not a dependency of this project:
            spring-expression, spring-webmvc, spring-webflux and spring-websocket respectively are all absent from
            both the compileClasspath and runtimeClasspath configurations.
            spring-core and spring-beans are only pulled in transitively via org.flowable:flowable-engine.
            Searching the compiled classes of every org.flowable jar (flowable-engine, flowable-engine-common, and
            all other flowable-* modules on the classpath) for any reference to org/springframework/* returns no
            matches at all, so Flowable does not call into AntPathMatcher or any other spring-core/spring-beans
            class either. The vulnerable code is therefore unreachable for all four CVEs.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.springframework/spring-(core|beans)@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41850</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41848</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41842</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41838</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-54428 (HTTP/2 HPACK decoder DoS) and CVE-2026-54399 (HTTP/1.1 message parser DoS) both affect
            Apache HttpComponents Core 5.x (5.4.2 and earlier / 5.5-beta1 and earlier), i.e. the org.apache.hc.core5
            codebase that ships in the org.apache.httpcomponents.core5:httpcore5 / httpcore5-h2 artifacts.
            This project depends on the legacy, unrelated 4.x line (org.apache.httpcomponents:httpcore, package
            org.apache.http.*), pulled in transitively via httpclient:4.5.14 <- org.apache.solr:solr-solrj. The 4.x
            codebase was rewritten from scratch for 5.x and does not implement HTTP/2 at all, so it cannot contain
            the vulnerable HPACK decoder, and its HTTP/1.1 parser is different code than the one fixed upstream.
            httpcore5 / httpclient5 are not dependencies of this project. This is a known NVD/CPE name-collision
            false positive between the 4.x and 5.x httpcore artifact families.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.apache\.httpcomponents/httpcore@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54428</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54399</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-5795 is a broken access control / privilege escalation issue caused by JASPIAuthenticator
            leaving ThreadLocal values set across requests. That class lives in Jetty's server-side jetty-security
            / jetty-jaspi module.
            This project only depends on Jetty's client-side modules (jetty-client, jetty-io, jetty-http,
            jetty-util, jetty-alpn-client, jetty-alpn-java-client, http2-client, http2-common,
            http2-http-client-transport), pulled in transitively via org.apache.solr:solr-solrj as its HTTP/2
            client transport. Confirmed there is no jetty-server, jetty-security or jetty-jaspi module anywhere in
            the dependency graph, so the vulnerable class is not present at all.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.eclipse\.jetty.*@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-5795</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2025-11143 (differential URI parsing security bypass) and CVE-2026-6790 (request authority /
            Host header mismatch not enforced) both describe attack scenarios where an untrusted, externally
            supplied URI or Host header is interpreted differently by Jetty than by another component in the
            request path (a WAF, reverse proxy, or the server generating a redirect) - i.e. they are server-side
            request-handling concerns.
            This project only uses Jetty's client-side modules (jetty-client, jetty-http, jetty-io, jetty-util,
            jetty-alpn-client, jetty-alpn-java-client, http2-client, http2-common, http2-http-client-transport),
            pulled in transitively via org.apache.solr:solr-solrj as its HTTP/2 client transport, to make outbound
            requests to our own configured Solr endpoint. There is no jetty-server in the dependency graph, no
            reverse proxy/WAF pair whose differing interpretation of the same URI could be exploited, and the
            target URI/Host header pair used for these outbound requests is not attacker-controlled. The described
            bypass scenarios do not apply to an outbound-only HTTP client use case.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.eclipse\.jetty.*@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2025-11143</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-6790</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2024-9329 is an open redirect in the Eclipse GlassFish *application server*'s admin console, via
            the Host header on its '/management/domain' management REST endpoint.
            relaxng-datatype and rngom are unrelated XML RELAX NG schema datatype libraries, part of the
            Eclipse/GlassFish *JAXB* project (org.glassfish.jaxb), pulled in transitively via
            org.jboss.resteasy:resteasy-jaxb-provider -> resteasy-multipart-provider. This application is deployed
            on WildFly, not GlassFish, does not embed the GlassFish application server or its admin console, and
            has no '/management/domain' endpoint. This is an NVD/CPE name-collision false positive between the
            unrelated "GlassFish" application server product and the "GlassFish JAXB" reference implementation
            project that happen to share the glassfish name.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/com\.sun\.xml\.bind\.external/(relaxng-datatype|rngom)@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2024-9329</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-0871 is an improper access control flaw in Keycloak's handling of "unmanaged" user profile
            attributes. Per the GitHub Security Advisory, the actually affected Maven package is
            org.keycloak:keycloak-server-spi-private (< 26.5.2) - a Keycloak *server*-side SPI module.
            keycloak-admin-client and keycloak-client-common-synced are unrelated client SDK artifacts used by this
            application only to call the Keycloak Admin REST API of an externally deployed Keycloak server; they do
            not contain keycloak-server-spi-private or the vulnerable authorization logic. This repository does not
            build or embed the Keycloak server itself, so this CVE is not fixable from this codebase - the actual
            Keycloak server instance this application connects to should be kept at >= 26.5.2 independently.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.keycloak/keycloak-(admin-client|client-common-synced)@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-0871</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            The following CVEs all require a Spring module that is not a dependency of this project:
            - CVE-2026-22737 (script template view path traversal), CVE-2026-22740 (WebFlux multipart temp file
              leak), CVE-2026-22745 (MVC/WebFlux static resource DoS on Windows), CVE-2026-41839 (WebFlux session
              fixation), CVE-2026-41840 (WebFlux multipart memory leak), CVE-2026-41841 (MVC/WebFlux static resource
              info disclosure), CVE-2026-41843 (MVC/WebFlux static resource path traversal), CVE-2026-41844
              (MVC/WebFlux open redirect via "/**" mapping) and CVE-2026-41853 (MVC/WebFlux multipart request
              smuggling) all require spring-webmvc and/or spring-webflux.
            - CVE-2026-41845 (JavaScriptUtils XSS) and CVE-2026-41854 (UriComponentsBuilder SSRF) both require
              spring-web (org.springframework.web.util package).
            - CVE-2026-41846 (JSP form tag XSS) requires the spring-webmvc JSP tag library.
            spring-webmvc, spring-webflux and spring-web are all absent from both the compileClasspath and
            runtimeClasspath configurations - this application is a Jakarta EE/JAX-RS app on WildFly and does not
            use Spring MVC/WebFlux at all. spring-core and spring-beans are only pulled in transitively via
            org.flowable:flowable-engine, which (as established for CVE-2026-41851/41850/41848/41842/41838 above)
            does not call into any org.springframework class.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.springframework/spring-(core|beans)@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-22737</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-22740</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-22745</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41839</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41840</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41841</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41843</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41844</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41845</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41846</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41853</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41854</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-41852 is a Spring Expression Language (SpEL) authorization bypass allowing arbitrary
            zero-argument method invocation, in the org.springframework.expression.spel package shipped in the
            spring-expression artifact. As established above for CVE-2026-41851/41850, spring-expression is not a
            dependency of this project at all, and Flowable (the only consumer of spring-core/spring-beans) does
            not use Spring's SpEL evaluator, so this code path is unreachable.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/org\.springframework/spring-(core|beans)@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-41852</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
            CVE-2026-54514 (SSRF via eager DNS resolution in JDKFromStringDeserializer), CVE-2026-54515 and
            CVE-2026-54516 (JsonIgnore/JsonProperty exclusion bypass), and CVE-2026-54517 and CVE-2026-54518
            (@JsonView filter bypass) all affect jackson-databind versions that include 2.21.1, fixed in 2.18.8/
            2.18.9, 2.21.4/2.21.5 and 3.1.4 depending on the specific CVE.
            As established for CVE-2026-54513 above, this jackson-databind 2.21.1 is only pulled in transitively
            (via org.wildfly.security:wildfly-elytron-jose-util -> wildfly-elytron-http-oidc) into the
            providedCompile and providedRuntime configurations - compile-only scope against APIs supplied by
            WildFly at deploy time, not packaged into the deployable artifact. The application's actual runtime and
            compile classpaths resolve jackson-databind to 2.22.1 via the jackson-bom pin in
            gradle/libs.versions.toml, which is already fixed for every one of these CVEs.
        ]]></notes>
        <packageUrl regex="true">^pkg:maven/com\.fasterxml\.jackson\.core/jackson-databind@.*$</packageUrl>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54514</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54515</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54516</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54517</vulnerabilityName>
        <vulnerabilityName>CVE-2026-54518</vulnerabilityName>
    </suppress>
</suppressions>
